how can what you want it to be you're
Frozen when your heart's not open
I could your
heart we
[Music]
never if I could live your
heart we never be
while I go to to while I go to You Make
Me For Your Love go on my knees and I
pray to the Lord after all you have
taken it all everything I got you have
taken it all baby I've been there for so
long now you say you don't want this no
more I've been waiting waiting far
aside you delay me playing wasting time
don't make me waitting L don't make me
waste my time I've been waiting all my
life and I thought
[Music]
you I thought you love me I thought you
me I tried to take care of your but's
Frozen why can't you show me don't leave
me
open I thought you told me that you're
ready but you
broken oh
yeah oh
yeah be
a yeah goodness
never